<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tahoe Ogul Peaks :: Mischa Friegang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/index.html</link>
    <description>The Tahoe Ogul list is a list created by a now disbanded chapter of the Sierra Club, the Peak and Gorge Section. “Ogul” is the Washoe word for bighorn sheep.&#xA;I started climbing this list (inadvertently) in 2015. I continued to slowly chip away until spring of 2023, when I set the goal of finishing the remaining 40 I had left before the end of July 2024. I managed to meet my goal, and had a great time doing so. The list got me out to amazing places I’d never have visited.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #63 - Raymond Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/raymond-peak-7-10-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/raymond-peak-7-10-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;After a night at one of my favorite campsites along Blue Lakes Road, I set off at a leisurely time of 7:30 or so towards the trailhead. The drive was fairly short, putting me at the “trailhead” around 7:45. I was using the forest service topo map as my guide, which didn’t quite lead me to the proper trailhead at Wet Meadow Reservoir, but I figured it was close enough. I parked my truck, and started walking up the muddy road to find where the actual PCT crossed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #62 - Snow Valley Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/snow-valley-peak-7-9-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/snow-valley-peak-7-9-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 9th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;Due to the blisters I had acquired on Anderson Peak and Tinker Knob, I had spent the previous day at home. I was planning to spend this day at home as well, but changed my mind around midday. The plan then morphed into me showing up at the trailhead around 3PM, and enjoying a nice twilight hike. My plan came to fruition, and I arrived at nearly precisely 3PM. The July heatwave was still very much a thing, and I was already sweating by the time I had put on my shoes and saddled up my backpack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #61 - English Mountain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/english-mountain-7-7-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/english-mountain-7-7-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 7th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;Chris and I had a good time the night before hanging out at our campsite. We had finally tracked down the allusive alcoholic Arizona Iced Teas, which we drank to our hearts content. My alarm went off at 5AM, and I was a bit tired from the night’s festivities, but I quickly loaded my truck up and set off for English Mountain, doing my best not to be too loud as Chris was still sleeping. I found some service along Bowman Lake road, and used that opportunity to set a destination in Google Maps. I saw that it was 17 miles down the road, but that Google said it would be over an hour. At this point, I knew I had some rough driving ahead of me. In hindsight, taking highway 89 to Jackson Meadows would have been a much more pleasant drive. The road indeed took over an hour, and required some moderate 4 wheeling at one point, I definitely would not try this road without at least a high clearance vehicle, and not with 2 wheel drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #59 and #60 - Anderson Peak and Tinker Knob</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/anderson-peak-tinker-knob-7-6-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/anderson-peak-tinker-knob-7-6-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 6th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I took some time off of work, with the plan of knocking out the rest of the Ogul Peaks. Thankfully, I had gotten more done before the trip than I had expected when I requested the time a few months prior, so my week wasn’t looking too difficult. To get things kicked off, I talked Chris into joining me for a double peak day, in addition to a section of the PCT we hadn’t done before. We met at the Palisades Tahoe Parking lot at 6:30AM. We left my truck there, and hopped into Chris’ car to head up to Donner Summit. By about 7:15, we were on the PCT headed south. The first mile or so went up some switchbacks and gained a good bit of elevation, passing by Mt Judah and Mt Lincoln, which I recognized from snowboarding at Sugar Bowl when I was a kid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #58 - Mt Fillmore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-fillmore-7-4-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-fillmore-7-4-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 4th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;We woke up after a night of little sleep, we forgot our dog’s bed, so he was restlessly walking around the truck bed all night. Despite being tired, we woke up and cooked breakfast and made coffee so that we could get an early start on the day. After breakfast, we broke everything down and set off down the dirt road back to highway 49. The road out from the trailhead isn’t bad, but has enough ruts and rocks to be a bit slow going. Little did I know that this was just a small sample of what was in store for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #57 - Haskell Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/haskell-peak-7-3-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/haskell-peak-7-3-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I worked on this day, but was able to shift my schedule up an hour, so that we could leave around 4pm that afternoon. The plan was to drive up to the Haskell Peak Trailhead, and quickly bag the peak before sundown. My wife and dog joined me on the drive up, but I would go solo on the hike. The plan worked out about as well as one could hope, and we were on the road by 4:15 or so. We made good time up highways 80 and 89, and were oat the trailhead by about 7:20PM. I grabbed my pretty minimal backpack, and set off within 10 minutes of arriving. I couldn’t quite figure out where the trailhead was, so ended up cutting across some bushes for about a hundred yards before joining up with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #55 and 56 - Needle Peak and Lyon Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/needle-lyon-6-23-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/needle-lyon-6-23-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>June 23rd, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I was on a bit of a tear for the week, having done 3 Ogul Peaks already, so I wanted to keep the streak going. I asked my Dad if he’d be interested in taking the tram at Palisades Tahoe up to access some peaks, and he liked the idea. Him and I climbed Granite Chief via the Granite Chief trail in 2016, so it didn’t really feel like we’d be missing much by taking the ride up. I also further justified it to myself by thinking of how much of a commonplace this kind of thing is in the Alps. We may not have nearly as much infrastructure in the Sierra, but I’m happy to take advantage when I can. I also talked my wife into coming up with us for the day so she could go paddle around the lake near Tahoe City on her SUP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #53 and 54 - Devil&#39;s Peak and Snow Mountain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/devils-peak-snow-mountain-6-19-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/devils-peak-snow-mountain-6-19-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>Full Image Gallery&#xA;June 19th, 2024 I woke up around 2AM, knowing that this would be a long day that involved at least some bushwhacking, how much exactly was unknown. The drive wasn’t too bad, although I did have to deal with some road work along highway 80 near Yuba Pass. I arrived at the trailhead around 4:45 and quickly got started down the Palisades Creek Trail. There was just enough light to not need my headlamp after a few minutes of letting my eyes adjust, so I walked in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #52 - South Sister</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/south-sister-6-16-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/south-sister-6-16-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>Full Image Gallery&#xA;June 16th, 2024 My dad and I had attempted South Sister the previous Father’s Day weekend. We ended up turning around at around 9k feet due to gale force winds, the kind of wind that literally can blow you off your feet. It was pretty unpleasant, but it made us both want to get back and bag the peak. Things lined up well for another Father’s Day trip, so we camped out Saturday night, and started early Saturday morning up one of the many rocky forest service roads that heads west from the Sweetwater Summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #51 - Mokelumne Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mokelumne-6-8-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mokelumne-6-8-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>June 8th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I had read up on Mokelumne Peak a bit over a year ago, and I knew this was one of the more remote peaks on the list. The minimum mileage you can find it listed at is around 14 miles round trip, but realistically it’s closer to 17+ miles, unless I’m missing some other approach that’s faster than the Tanglefoot Trailhead approach. That said, I decided to continue my trend of getting up at 3AM so I could make it home with some daylight left. I ended up snoozing my alarm, and being a bit slow to get out the door, so I arrived at the TH around 6AM. There was a van parked at the trailhead, and they had set up a tent in one of the only other parking spots. They also had left beer cans in the middle of the dirt road; I try not to hate the recent van life trend, but people like that give vans a really bad name. The road doesn’t dead end for another hundred yards or so, so I just continued down to the dead end and parked there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #50 - Highland Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/highland-peak-6-2-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/highland-peak-6-2-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>June 2nd, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;As is tradition, I woke up at the ungodly hour of 3AM for this hike. I was left a bit traumatized by the route Chris and I took the summer before up the adjoining Silver Peak, so wanted to get as much time as possible. Highland is a few hundred feet taller, and further away from the Noble Canyon Trailhead than Silver Peak. All that said, I was a bit apprehensive of this one. I arrived shortly after 6AM at the trailhead, and got moving quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #49 - Twin Peaks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/twin-peaks-5-19-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/twin-peaks-5-19-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 19th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I arrived at the Blackwood Canyon Sno Park around 6:40AM. The sno park had already started its transformation into a campsite parking lot for the summer, made evident by the “Campground Parking Only” signs posted at about half of the parking spots. I made sure to find one without that sign, saddled up my skis on my pack, and began walking up Blackwood Canyon Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #48 - Phipp&#39;s Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/phipps-peak-5-11-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/phipps-peak-5-11-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 11th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;They say adventure begins when things start to go wrong. By that logic, this trip became an adventure before I even got out of bed. I went to bed Friday night around 8:45, hoping to wake up at 4AM. I usually fall asleep without any issue, but on this night, I simply could not fall asleep. I decided to cut my losses around 1AM. Leaving a few hours early sounded a whole lot better than laying there and never falling asleep. I was out the door around 1:30, and at the Eagle Falls trailhead around 3:20AM, skis strapped to my backpack and ready to roll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #47 - Ellis Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/ellis-peak-4-27-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/ellis-peak-4-27-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>April 27th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;We originally had planned to do an overnight snow camping trip in Blackwood Canyon, and climb Ellis Peak. As the date got closer, I happened to stumble upon a forest service page mentioning that overnight camping was not allowed in that area, so the plan shifted towards a day trip. Chris and I met at his house at 5:30 and loaded into his Subaru. His dog, Cal would be joining us on the trip. We arrived at the Blackwood Canyon Sno Park around 8, and walked down the bike trail to a nearby road with a fire road easement leading into the forest service land. This allowed us to bypass crossing Blackwood Creek, which may have proven difficult with the spring melt happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #46 - Mt Elwell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-elwell-4-26-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-elwell-4-26-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>April 26th, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;With a fairly long drive ahead of me, I woke up at 3AM, and was on the road by 3:30AM or so. I took the day off about a month in advance, and with my luck it happened to land on a day with some weather in the forecast. Due to this, I made the call to take a trip up north where the snow doesn’t fall as deep as it does closer to Tahoe. The roads weren’t too bad, and I was at the Gold Lake Staging area by 6:45AM. The snow was basically gone at that elevation, so I decided to leave the skis in my truck for the day, and just focus on going light and fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #45 - Hawkins Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/hawkins-4-21-24/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/hawkins-4-21-24/index.html</guid>
      <description>April 21st, 2024 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I woke up at 3AM so that I could hopefully beat the snow warming up. The forecasted weather made me question if there would be much of a refreeze, so I wanted to get an early start. I was at the trailhead at Pickett Junction around 5AM. I loaded up all of my gear, and set off in my running shoes, hoping that the snow would be supportive enough to walk on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #44 - Mt Lola</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/lola-8-20-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/lola-8-20-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>August 20th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;We arrived at the trailhead around 8 AM. The weather was pretty cool and gloomy for August, but as someone who doesn’t enjoy heat, it was a welcome change for me. The drive out was a bit long, but pleasant. I really like the section of Highway 89 that’s north of Truckee. We saw one other group getting ready at the trailhead, but set off before they did. My Dad, as well as my Dog George were joining me for this hike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #43 - Mt Mildred</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mildred-8-13-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mildred-8-13-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>August 13th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;My dad joined me for Mt Mildred, and we decided to approach it from the Hell Hole side. Its a bit closer to where we live, and seemed like the less traveled route. I mapped out the route the best I could from blindly looking at forest service topo maps, and we drove my truck as far as we could up an old forest service road below Chipmunk Ridge, which leads towards the western flank of Mt Mildred. From where we parked, there was no trail, nor did we really ever find one all day. However, the ridge seemed like it would make navigating somewhat easy. We bushwhacked a bit up a steep hill, and gained the ridge in perhaps 20-30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #42 - Black Buttes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/black-buttes-7-29-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/black-buttes-7-29-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 29th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;My wife and dog joined me on this fine Saturday, we made the bumpy drive out to the Grouse Ridge trailhead. It wasn’t terrible, but definitely was slow going and quite dusty and bumpy. When we arrived, there were quite a few more cars than I had expected, turns out there’s a campground out there thats fairly popular. There was even a Honda Civic that had somehow managed to pull a trailer out there. Mad respect to that guy, he either knows a better route, or is quite the skilled driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #41 - Silver Peak - Southwest Summit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/silver-peak-7-22-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/silver-peak-7-22-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 22nd, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I met Chris in Placerville, and we carpooled up to Ebbett’s Pass, arriving around 7:30AM. Instead of going all the way to the pass, we parked a few turns east of it, at the Noble Lake Trailhead. We knew it was going to be somewhat hot, and definitely a struggle to get up based on what we had read about this route. Silver Peak is also an interesting Ogul peak in that the slightly lower southwest summit is the Ogul Peak, but not the high point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #40 - Sierra Buttes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/sierra-buttes-7-8-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/sierra-buttes-7-8-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 8th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;After a week out on the road camping and bagging peaks, it was still a weekend, and I talked my wife into bagging another Ogul peak with me. This was a good opportunity to take a nice drive together, as well as a nice hike. We left home around 7, and stopped for bagels in Auburn before getting on highway 49 towards Nevada City. I had never taken 49 beyond Grass Valley, and it was a nice drive. We passed through Downieville and decided we’d stop there on the way back to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #39 - Lookout Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/lookout-peak-7-7-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/lookout-peak-7-7-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 7th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I woke up for my last night out of the trip, hoping to knock out one more Ogul and get home at a reasonable time. Lookout Peak seemed to fit the bill nicely, it didn’t look too difficult on paper. The road to the Pacific Valley Campground was still snowed in, so I parked right by highway 4. This would add a few miles, but they were all easy flat miles. I was walking by 6:45, and was immediately impressed by how much snow was still there. It seemed that this area was pretty well shaded, causing the snow to linger for quite some time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #38 - Reynolds Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/reynolds-peak-7-6-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/reynolds-peak-7-6-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 6th, 2023 I woke up around 5AM at my campsite on Blue Lakes Road. It was a bit far from Ebbett’s Pass, but I had wanted somewhere with service so I could get some info for the next day. I packed up my camp, and drove to Ebbett’s Pass. The road to Ebbett’s Pass is pretty interesting, it completely forgoes the yellow line, and is about 1.5 cars wide over the top. I made it to the pass around 6:45 and crossed the road to find the PCT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #36 and 37 - Genoa Peak and Duane Bliss Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/genoa-duane-bliss-7-5-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/genoa-duane-bliss-7-5-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 5th, 2023 Chris returned home on the 5th, so it was down to just Jed and myself for the next leg of the journey. Jed was planning to head home after this one, and I was planning to stay out a few more nights. Wanting to get another double summit day, we decided on Genoa and Duane Bliss Peaks. They aren’t nearly as exciting as the other peaks we had done recently, but it would also allow us to knock out one of our last remaining sections of the TRT. Jed and I met at Spooner summit, and we got into his car to drive to the Daggett Trailhead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #34 and 35 - Da-Ek-Dow Go-Et and The Nipple</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/da-ek-dow-go-et-the-nipple-7-4-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/da-ek-dow-go-et-the-nipple-7-4-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 4th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;For our second stop on our peakbagging road trip, we camped on the side of Blue Lakes Road. Being the third of July, I was a bit pessimistic about finding a good place to camp, but we did end up finding a great place right by some running water. We woke up around 5 on the 4th and geared up for the day. We weren’t entirely sure about the snow, so we ended up bringing snowshoes just in case (we would later regret this decision).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #32 and #33 - Mt Patterson and Wheeler Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/patterson-wheeler-7-2-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/patterson-wheeler-7-2-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>July 2nd, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;Saturday morning (the 1st of July), I drove out to the Sweetwaters once again QA. This time, my friends Chris and Jed joined me as well. We had plans to move around to a few places and bag some peaks. They planned to stay until Wednesday and Thursday, and I planned to stay until Friday or Saturday. We made it out to our campsite near the creek that runs down Sweetwater Canyon. The creek was flowing pretty well, so they parked on the north side of the creek, and we loaded my truck up to cross the creek and get to the better campsite on the south side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #31 - Adams Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/adams-peak-6-24-23/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/adams-peak-6-24-23/index.html</guid>
      <description>June 24th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I planned this trip on a whim the Thursday before we went. Adams Peak is the furthest north of any peak on the Ogul list. I’ve been trying to knock out some of the furthest ones so I can eventually just have ones near Tahoe left, plus a lot of options are still unavailable to me after the insane winter we had. I wanted to go for a quick overnight camping trip with my wife and my dog, and Adams seemed to check all of the prerequisite boxes, so I took off work a few hours early Friday, and we started the drive up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #30 - Mt Rose</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-rose/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt-rose/index.html</guid>
      <description>June 3rd, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;My alarm went off at an ungodly 2AM on this fine Saturday morning. I had 2 parties to go to later that day, the first being at noon. I stubbornly refused to give up on bagging another Ogul this weekend, and Mt Rose seemed to make the most sense given a lot of factors (mostly snow and estimated time to the summit). I rolled out of bed, and made the long sleepy drive up to Mt Rose Summit via highway 80. I’m a big proponent of the alpine start, but what sucks about driving at 2AM is that you can’t see any of the scenery. Regardless, I made it to the trailhead and was walking by 4:48AM. I didn’t have a ton of info on the route, but understood there was a bridge somewhere over Galena Creek, and that I’d just need to aim for the east ridge. Easy stuff on paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #29 - Mt Siegel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt_siegel/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/mt_siegel/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 29th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I woke up at my campsite near Sonora Pass right around 4:40AM. It was 20 minutes before my alarm, but the desert birds had started their morning routine already. This was my third morning out there, and I knew that this meant the sun was coming up soon. I felt rested so I forced myself out of my down quilt, and started packing my truck up. I quickly broke camp and threw everything in my truck, on the road towards Gardnerville shortly after 5. The drive went by quickly, and I went straight to the Walmart there to grab some food for my excursion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #28 - Desert Creek Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/black-mountain-desert-creek/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/black-mountain-desert-creek/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 28th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I let myself sleep in until around 6 after doing East and Middle Sisters the day before. I figured Desert Creek Peak would be a relatively easy day in comparison. I packed all of my stuff into my truck, and drove down to where I had seen Desert Creek the day before. There ended up being some people camped here, so I decided I’d find some other place to park my truck. I had seen a side spur road about a mile south on my topo map, so decided to check that out. This road was near the base of Black Mountain, and I figured I could link the ridges between the 2 up. I had read a Bob Burd trip report about him doing both, but my memories were pretty fuzzy about the details. I didn’t have any service so I figured I’d just use my topo maps and wing it. I made it a decent ways up the spur road, and found a nice place to park my truck for the day. This was well off the beaten path, so I was pretty confident nobody would mess with my stuff. I loaded my day pack up, and was off shortly on my way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #26 and #27 - East and Middle Sister</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/east-middle-sisters/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/east-middle-sisters/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 27th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I took off work a few hours early at 3PM Friday, and already had mostly loaded my truck up for 3 days of camping. I had a few odds and ends to handle after, but was on the road by 3:30PM or so. I stopped to get gas and a few road snacks in Placerville, and was soon headed up highway 50. Somewhere shortly before Kyburz, it started to rain pretty hard. I stopped at the Silverfork store and moved a few things from my truck bed that weren’t waterproof into the cab. I made a quick stop in Gardnerville for some Jack in the Box Tacos, and then headed down 395.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #25 - Job&#39;s Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/jobs-peak-5-20-2023/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/jobs-peak-5-20-2023/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 20th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;My alarm woke me up from a weird dream at 2:40AM. I can’t recall the specifics of it at this point, but I do recall there being some weird tribal music, kind of similar to the “Survivor” theme song. I hadn’t slept that well, and had a moderately painful lump in my throat the week leading up. Despite my discomfort, I had been dreaming about this peak all week. I did my morning routine as quietly as possible, and left my comfortable bed, wife and dog behind. I love them dearly, but this is more than they want to do in a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #24 - Wade Benchmark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/wade-benchmark-5-13-2023/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/wade-benchmark-5-13-2023/index.html</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;I woke up early again for this one, we had enjoyed a nice dip in temps, along with some precipitation the previous week. I even got in a rare May pow day the previous Sunday. Looking at the forecast though, it was pretty clear that this Saturday was set to be significantly hotter. I wanted to knock another Ogul peak off, and initially had planned to go climb Mt Rose. I left the house around 3:15AM, and while driving over Echo Summit got the idea to knock Wade off instead of Rose, and save the hour of driving. I wasn’t entirely sure that the trailhead would be thawed out, but I had a feeling it likely would be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ogul #23 - Rubicon Peak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/rubicon-peak-4-8-2023/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/outdoor-trip-reports/ogul-peaks/rubicon-peak-4-8-2023/index.html</guid>
      <description>April 8th, 2023 Full Image Gallery&#xA;My goal this winter has simply been to log as many days as possible on my splitboard. It brings me joy regardless of the conditions, a day out splitboarding is a good day. That said, I’ve also been (very) slowly chipping away at the Tahoe Ogul Peak List, and Rubicon was one of the closer ones that I hadn’t ticked off yet. In addition, the conditions lined up in a way that the snow would probably still be decent there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>